We'll be right back.
Come back, Robin.
Showdown with CP9.
Oh, yeah.
Those are the same guys that were with you back at the shipyard, right?
Right?
Actually, that square-nosed guy came to our ship.
I see.
And the attack on Iceberg was an inside job.
Wait, what?
I don't get it.
Paulie, in all honesty, we're secret agents working for the world government.
But hey, you'll forgive me if I say I'm sorry, right?
We were comrades, building ships together every day from dawn till dusk.
I realize this is quite sudden for you, so perhaps you'd believe me if I smashed Iceberg's face.
Just shut the hell up.
I've heard enough.
You were that guy in the bull mask, weren't you?
That was the first time I ever heard your voice.
All those years, you never said a word.
But you can talk just fine.
I'll teach you to make fun of me!
Paulie, stop it!
Pipe.
Hitch.
Knife!
Bring your pistol.
You still haven't learned your lesson, have you?
Hey, are you okay?
Screw you.
Lucci.
It's pointless to resist.
Our abilities far exceed those of a normal human, as you can see.
After many years of training, we've mastered an art called the Six Powers.
These techniques transform the body into a living weapon with the strength of over a hundred men.
Cuckoo!
Stop drinking, Paulie!
What about all that debt?
Come on!
I want some cash today.
Next round's on me, okay?
Bring it, Bluno.
Let's go!
You got it.
Callie for you, Hussie!
That skirt is way too short!
Hey, give it a rest, Paulie.
If you don't like it, don't look at her, okay?
After all his time, why?
Sorry, Paulie.
Our friendship is over.
I have to eliminate you.
Lucci!
No, don't!
You jerk!
Leave him alone!
Gumsho entreg!
I embody Godland!
What the? That didn't work at all.
You're nothing but a pest, Shave.
He's gone.
Finger pistol.
If you weren't made out of rubber, you'd be dead with a hole in your neck.
Lucky you.
You're protecting him. But why?
Why not? Because I don't want you to kill him!
You guys were all friends just the other day. How could you do this?
We were. Now, things have changed.
It doesn't matter. You can say what you want. You're a bunch of traitors.
The point is, you're my enemy now.
I made a promise with Polly to beat the crap out of anybody who tries to hurt Ice Pops.
I see. You decided to trust him over us, huh?
That's right. Because you guys took away one of my friends!
Hey, Robin, what gives? Why are you acting like this?
If you want to leave the crew, at least tell me why!
Yeah, and why would you want to team up with people from the world government? That's crazy!
Do I have to repeat myself? I believe I said my farewells to the cook and the doctor before I left.
Didn't you pass that along, Chopper?
Of course I did! But just because I heard it doesn't mean I accept it! How could you do this?
I did it to make my wish come true. A wish that can't happen as long as we're together.
And if you can't accept that, I'm sorry.
You may not find it fair, but to accomplish my goal, I'll make any sacrifice.
I see. And that includes framing your own crewmates for attempted murder. So what is this wish of yours?
I don't have to answer that question.
Are you out of your mind? Wake up, Robin. You have no right to do this. I don't care what it is you're trying to accomplish. The consequences are far too great.
I've heard enough. This is no longer your choice to make.
This should shut you up.
No! Iceberg!
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Nothing you're saying is making any sense! You expect me to believe this?
Robin! What happened to you?
You're our friend, Rice! Please, Robin! Come back!
Sorry to break up the reunion, but I'll have to stop you there.
You see, we have a date this evening with a very important individual.
One that's been over four years in the making.
We're finished here.
In other words, that means we're finished with you as well.
Khalifa, how much time is left?
Two minutes.
Here's the deal.
I know this is sudden, but in two minutes, this building will go up in a ball of flame.
You're kidding!
Of course not.
Fire is an effective tool for erasing all sorts of evidence.
If you don't want to be burned alive, I suggest you leave the building as soon as possible.
Oh, well, I say that.
But I have no intention of letting you go.
Looks like it's going to be us against them, and our friend Robin has clearly picked her side.
Luffy, Robin is not one of us anymore.
Do you accept that now?
No! No way!
So noisy.
Anyway, the first floor is about to set fire.
It won't be pretty.
But to be fair, the culprits are just pirates.
You can't expect them to be subtle.
You bastards!
That's nice of you to give us credit for your attempted arson, but I think that I'll pass.
What's one more crime when we're going to execute you anyway?
Well, I suppose I'll take my leave now.
You've done exactly as you were told.
Good work.
Robin!
Don't go!
You're still one of us!
This is farewell.
Robin!
Stop her.
Straw hat.
We finally found you!
I won't let you run away again!
Out of my way!
Iron body.
Hmm.
How come nothing I do to these guys even phases them?
In addition to our offensive techniques, our training has also given us the ability to make our body as solid as an iron wall.
Of course, your punches are weak to begin with.
Okay, whatever!
I said out of my way!
Paper art.
Even though he's big, he sure is fast!
He's moving like his body's made of paper!
Oh no!
Robin!
Move it!
Come on!
Pistol!
Shave!
He disappeared!
My legs are so strong that I can move faster than your eyes can see.
Stand still!
Moon walk.
In fact, I can even leap off of the air itself.
He's flying!
Tempest!
Kick!
A slashing attack?
Get down!
Hurry!
Why?
Luffy!
They did all that with a single kick?
No way!
Technically, it was the sharp gust of wind that followed it.
We call it the tempest kick.
We met on your ship.
疲れ果てた向きの中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつか辿り着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に 見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸辿り 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた晴れ渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に 永遠に
実際にとって 実際には大きめが大きい break ボシッシュのようだ
King of the Pirates!